Guide to the PricewaterhouseCoopers Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Coopers & Lybrand Series VII: Moving Image
  - Subseries VII.2: General
    - Spirit of Teamwork, Jul. 1988, RT: 6 min (VHS preservation master) (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Springboard/SSA On-Line - Internal Version, n.d., RT: 8:30 (VHS preservation master) (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Freedman, Eugene M. State of the Firm by Gene Freedman, Dec. 1992, RT: 14 min (VHS preservation master) (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Jacobs, John State of the Practice by John Jacobs, V.C., Apr. 29, 1996, RT: 13:00 (VHS preservation master) (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Supporting Youth Education, Aug. 8, 1989, VHS preservation master) (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Technology in Action, Jul. 1986, VHS preservation master) (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Telecommications: NY Telephone and NE Telephone spots, Apr. 1986, VHS preservation master) (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Times Are Changing, n.d., RT: 00:60 (VHS preservation master) (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - UAA Comparisons withLybrand Approach, Part 1, n.d., VHS preservation master) (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - M. Howard Productions Values From the Past, Vision For the Future, Oct. 15, 1993, RT: 14:40 (VHS preservation master), 2 (VHS reference copy, Sep. 7, 1994) (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Values From the Past, Vision For the Future - Revision, Sep. 12, 1995, RT: 13:45 (VHS preservation master) (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Coppola, Victor Victor Coppola Reshoot, Tape 1, 5-May-87, VHS preservation master) (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Auerbach, Norman E. Viewpoint: The Metcalf Report. A Discussion with Norman E. Auerbach, RT: 33:00 (3/4 inch U-Matic preservation master) (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - A Vision of Technology, Aug. 1990, VHS preservation master) (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Steve Zahler Productions Winners in the 90s, Jan. 17, 1996, RT: 24:37 (VHS preservation master) (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Winning Through Values, 1990s, VHS preservation master) (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - You and Your Future, Sep. 1989, RT: 5 min (VHS preservation master) (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Unmarked tapes, 3 (VHS) (Box 40, Folder 25 - 27)
  - Subseries VII.3: Retirement Parties
    Alphabetical by name
    - Abrahams, Martin Bob Thomas Productions Marty Abrahams Retirement Dinner, Oct. 19, 1995, RT: 2 hrs. (VHS preservation master), 1 (VHS reference copy) (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Bazaar, Harvey Harvey Bazaar Retirement Dinner, Jun. 7, 2000, VHS preservation master) (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Burris, Barry Bob Thomas Productions Barry Burris Retirement Party, Rainbow Room Club, [New York, NY], Nov. 9, 1994, RT: 1.5 hrs. (S-VHS camera original preservation master ), 1 (VHS reference copy) (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Clarke, James Jim Clarke Retirement Dinner, Rolls 1, 2, Oct. 2, 1999, 2 tapes (VHS preservation master) (Box 40, Folder 31 - 32)
    - Ellenberger, Bert Bert Ellenberger Retirement Party, Apr. 2, 1998, VHS preservation master) (Box 40, Folder 33)
    - Fitzpatrick, Thomas Thomas Fitzpatrick Retirement Party, 15-May-97, RT: 2 hrs. (VHS camera original preservation master ) (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Hackman, Ray Bob Thomas Productions Day in Life of Ray Hackman, [Sep. 21, 1995], RT: 22:14 (3/4 inch U-Matic preservation master), 1 (VHS reference copy) (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - Hackman, Ray Bob Thomas Productions Ray Hackman Retirement Dinner, Rolls 1, 2, Sep. 21, 1995, 2 tapes (VHS camera original preservation master ), 1 (2 tapes) (VHS reference copy) (Box 41, Folder 2 - 3)
    - Henry, Robert J. E. Robert J. E. Henry Retirement Party, Tapes 1, 2, Jan. 6, 1998, 2 tapes (VHS camera original preservation master ), 1 (tape 2 only) (VHS reference copy) (Box 41, Folder 4 - 5)
    - Jacey, Charles Charles Jacey Retirement Party, Essex House, New York, NY, Jan. 31, 1998, RT: 1:54:00 (VHS preservation master) (Box 41, Folder 6)
      [Speeches begin at 56:10]
    - Jones, Seymour; Bob Thomas Productions Seymour Jones Retirement Party - roll 2, Oct. 26, 1995, VHS preservation master) (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Lis, Stephen Stepen Liz Retirement Party, Oct. 8, 1999, VHS preservation master), 1 (VHS reference copy) (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - McKessy, Stephen Timeframe Productions Steve McKessy Video Tribute Featuring John Jacobs, 14-May-98, VHS preservation master) (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - McKessy, Stephen Steve McKessy Retirement Party at the Plaza, The Plaza, New York, NY, 16-May-98, VHS preservation master) (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Murray, Ronald Bob Thomas Productions Mr. Ron Murray Retirement Party, Pavillion Room, [New York, NY], Oct. 29, 1996, VHS preservation master) (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Coopers & Lybrand Series VIII: Art and Ephemera
  Portraits, plaques, commemorative buttons, items bearing company logos etc.
  - Turn of the Century Images, Philadelphia, PA, [1890s], 1 (magazine illustrations) (Box 347, Folder 4)
  - Staub, Walter; Montgomery Robert Mounted Portraits, n.d., 3 (14 x 12 ) (Box 347, Folder 5)
    [Staub's autoghaph on portrait]
  - Jones, Seymour; Lenhart, Norman J.; Mahon, James; Rappaport, Louis H; Schaffer, Walter L.; Walsh, Joseph S.; Wintrub, Warren G. Distingushed Partners - portraits by S. Bruce Morser, [1994-1996], 7 (pencil drawings, framed) (Box 347, Folder 6)
  - Evolution of the Internet Poster, [1995], 1 (24 x 36) (Box 347, Folder 7)
  - C&L Values plaque, 1990s, 1 (10.5 x 14) (Box 347, Folder 8)
  - C&L: A Professional Services Firm Folder, n.d., 1 (10 x 12) (Box 347, Folder 9)
  - C&L Foundation Room plaque, [1980s], 1 (4.5 x 9) (Box 348)
  - Cordier' Andrew W. Columbia University, President Plaque featuring Thank You Letter to Louis H. Rappaport on behalf of alumni phase of Columbia $200 campaign, New York, NY, Aug. 1, 1971, 1 (10 x 12, wood) (Box 348)
  - Pace College Benefactor plaque for RBML, New York, NY, n.d. (Box 348)
  - Summer Jobs '86 buttons, New York, NY, 1986, 2 (3'' buttons) (Box 348)
  - C&L apron, n.d., 1 (cotton apron, red/white) (Box 348)
- Coopers & Lybrand Series IX: Books and Monographs
  Series consists of books and monographs from the C&L library, printed by or relating to RBML and C&L
  - Subseries IX.1: Heritage of Robert Montgomery
    - Montgomery, Robert H, Auditing, Parts I, II, III., Chicago: American School of Correspondence, 1909, 3 volumes) (Box 42)
      [vols 1, 3 need repair]
    - Montgomery, Robert H, Auditing Theory and Practice, First Edition, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1912, 1913, 2 copies ( (Box 42)
      [need repair]
    - Montgomery, Robert H, Montgomery, Robert H, Auditing Theory and Practice, Student Edition, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1915 (Box 42)
      [needs repair]
    - Montgomery, Robert H, Auditing Theory and Practice, Second Edition, First Printing, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1916 (Box 42)
    - Montgomery, Robert H, Auditing Theory and Practice, Second Edition, Ninth Printing, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1920 (Box 43)
    - Montgomery, Robert H, Auditing Theory and Practice, Third Edition, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1921, 2 volumes) (Box 43)
    - Montgomery, Robert H, Auditing Theory and Practice, Fouth Edition Revised and Enlarged, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1927 (Box 43)
      [Signed by H. F. Bell]
    - Montgomery, Robert H, Auditing Theory and Practice, Fifth Edition, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1934 (Box 43)
    - Montgomery, Robert H, Auditing Theory and Practice, Sixth Edition, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1940 (Box 43)
      [Inscribed by Montgomery to Wm M. Lybrand, Nov. 18, 1940. Needs repair]
    - Montgomery, Robert H.; Lenhart, Norman J.; Jennings, Alvin R. Auditing Theory and Practice, Seventh Edition, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1949 (Box 43)
    - Lenhart, Norman J.; Jennings, Alvin R. Montgomery's Auditing, Eighth Edition, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1957 (Box 43)
      [Continuation of Auditing Theory and Practice]
    - Defliese, Philip L.; Johnson, Kenneth P.; Macleod, Roderick K. Montgomery's Auditing, Ninth Edition, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1975 (Box 43)
      [Inscribed by Defliese to Firm Library, Dec, 1975]
    - Sullivan, Jerry D.; Gnospelius, Richard A.; Defliese, Philip L.; Jaenicke, Henry R. Montgomery's Auditing, Tenth Edition. - College Version, New York: John Wiley & Sons, Inc., The Ronald Press Publication, 1984 (Box 43)
      [Signed by authors]
    - Sullivan, Jerry D.; Gnospelius, Richard A.; Defliese, Philip L.; Jaenicke, Henry R. Montgomery's Auditing, Tenth Edition, New York: John Wiley & Sons, Inc., The Ronald Press Publication, 1985 (Box 43)
    - Sullivan, Jerry D.; Gnospelius, Richard A.; Defliese, Philip L.; Jaenicke, Henry R. Montgomery's Auditing, Tenth Edition. - Revised College Version, New York: John Wiley & Sons, Inc., The Ronald Press Publication, 1987 (Box 43)
    - O;Reilly, Vincent M.; Hirsch, Murray B.; Defliese, Philip L.; Jaenicke, Henry R. Montgomery's Auditing, Eleventh Edition, New York: John Wiley & Sons, Inc., The Ronald Press Publication, 1990 (Box 43)
    - O;Reilly, Vincent M.; Hirsch, Murray B.; Defliese, Philip L.; Jaenicke, Henry R. Montgomery's Auditing, Eleventh Edition - College Version, New York: John Wiley & Sons, Inc., The Ronald Press Publication, 1990 (Box 43)
    - Montgomery, Robert H. Income Tax Procedure, First Printing, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1917 (Box 44)
      [Inscribed by Montgomery to Walter Staub, Jan. 11, 1917]
    - Montgomery, Robert H. Income Tax Procedure, Second Printing, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1917 (Box 42)
    - Montgomery, Robert H. Income Tax Procedure, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1918 (Box 42)
      [Office Copy, signed by Montgomery]
    - Montgomery, Robert H. Income Tax Procedure, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1919, 1 vol. + supplement) (Box 44)
    - Montgomery, Robert H. Income Tax Procedure, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1920 (Box 44)
      [Inscribed by Montgomery to Wm M. Lybrand, Feb. 9, 1920]
    - Montgomery, Robert H. Income Tax Procedure, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1921 (Box 44)
      [Inscribed by Montgomery to Wm M. Lybrand, Feb. 7, 1921]
    - Montgomery, Robert H. Income Tax Procedure, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1922 (Box 44)
      [Inscribed by Montgomery to sister [Lenore] Montgomery Lybrand, Mar. 31, 1922]
    - Montgomery, Robert H. Income Tax Procedure, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1923 (Box 44)
      [Inscribed by Montgomery to Wm M. Lybrand, Dec. 29, 1922]
    - Montgomery, Robert H. Income Tax Procedure, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1924 (Box 44)
    - Montgomery, Robert H. Income Tax Procedure, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1925 (Box 44)
      [Montgomery's personal copy]
    - Montgomery, Robert H. Income Tax Procedure, Vol. I, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1926, Vol I of 2) (Box 44)
      [Volume 2 (Excess Profits, Estate, Gift, Capital Stock Tax Procedure) not found]
    - Montgomery, Robert H. Income Tax Procedure, Vols. I, II, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1927, 2 volumes) (Box 44)
      [Signed by H. F. Bell (Vol. I)]
    - Montgomery, Robert H. Income Tax Procedure (Supplement to 1927 Income Tax Procedure), New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1929 (Box 44)
    - Montgomery, Robert H. Montgomery's Federal Taxes on Corporations, 1942-43, Vols. I, II, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1943, 2 volumes) (Box 45)
    - Montgomery, Robert H. Montgomery's Federal Taxes on Corporations, 1943-44, Vols. I, II, with enclosed notes on the Revenue Act of 1943, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1943, 2 volumes) (Box 45)
      [Signed by Staub.]
    - Montgomery, Robert H. Montgomery's Federal Taxes on Corporations, 1944-45, Vols I, II, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1945, 2 volumes) (Box 45)
    - Montgomery, Robert H. Montgomery's Federal Taxes on Corporations, 1945-46, Vols. I, II, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1946, 2 volumes) (Box 45)
    - Montgomery, Robert H.; Taylor, Conrad B.; Richardson, Mark E. Montgomery's Federal Taxes: Corporations and Partnerships, 1946-47, Vols. I, II, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1947, 2 volumes) (Box 45)
    - Montgomery, Robert H.; Taylor, Conrad B.; Richardson, Mark E. Montgomery's Federal Taxes: Corporations and Partnerships, 1947-48, Vols. I, II, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1948, 2 volumes) (Box 45)
    - Montgomery, Robert H.; Taylor, Conrad B.; Richardson, Mark E. Montgomery's Federal Taxes: Corporations and Partnerships, 1948-49, Vols. I, II, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1948, 2 volumes) (Box 45)
    - Montgomery, Robert H.; Taylor, Conrad B.; Richardson, Mark E. Montgomery's Federal Taxes: Corporations and Partnerships, 1949-50, Vol. I, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1950, 2 volumes) (Box 45)
      [Vol. 2 in box 46]
    - Montgomery, Robert H.; Taylor, Conrad B.; Richardson, Mark E. Montgomery's Federal Taxes: Corporations and Partnerships, 1949-50, Vol. II, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1950, 2 volumes) (Box 46)
      [Vol. 1 in box 45]
    - Montgomery, Robert H.; Taylor, Conrad B.; Richardson, Mark E. Montgomery's Federal Taxes: Corporations and Partnerships, 1950-51, Vols. I, II, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1951, 2 volumes) (Box 46)
    - Montgomery, Robert H.; Taylor, Conrad B.; Richardson, Mark E. Montgomery's Federal Taxes 1951-52: Corporations and Partnerships, Vols. I, II, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1952, 2 volumes) (Box 46)
    - Montgomery, Robert H.; Wynn, James O.; Blattmachr, G. Harold Montgomery's Federal Taxes 1951-52: Estates, Trusts and Gifts, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1952 (Box 46)
    - Bardes, Philip; Mahon, James J.; McCullough, John; Richardson, Mark E. Montgomery's Federal Taxes, 35th Edition, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1954 (Box 46)
    - Bardes, Philip; Mahon, James J.; McCullough, John; Richardson, Mark E. Montgomery's Federal Taxes, 36th Edition, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1955 (Box 46)
      [Signed by Walter Staub]
    - Bardes, Philip; Mahon, James J.; McCullough, John; Richardson, Mark E. Montgomery's Federal Taxes, 37th Edition, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1958 (Box 46)
    - Bardes, Philip; Fish, James B.; McCullough, John; Richardson, Mark E.; Herman Stuetzer, Jr., Paul D. Yager, eds. Montgomery's Federal Taxes, 38th Edition, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1961 (Box 46)
    - Philip Bardes, William T. Barnes, James B. Fish, Herman Stuetzer, Jr., Paul D. Yager, eds. Montgomery's Federal Taxes, 39th Edition, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1964 (Box 46)
    - Montgomery, Robert H. Federal Tax Handbook: Revenue Act of 1932, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1932 (Box 47)
    - Montgomery, Robert H. Federal Tax Handbook: 1933-1934, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1933 (Box 47)
    - Montgomery, Robert H. Federal Tax Handbook: 1934-1935, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1934 (Box 47)
    - Montgomery, Robert H. Federal Tax Handbook: 1935-1936, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1935 (Box 47)
    - Montgomery, Robert H. Federal Tax Handbook: 1936-1937, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1936 (Box 47)
    - Montgomery, Robert H. Federal Tax Handbook: 1940-41, Vols. I, II, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1940, 2 volumes) (Box 47)
    - Montgomery, Robert H. Federal Tax Handbook Supplement: 1941-42, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1941 (Box 47)
    - Montgomery, Robert H. Federal Tax Practice, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1929 (Box 47)
      [Signed by C. B. Taylor]
    - Montgomery, Robert H. Federal Tax Practice. Revised Edition, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1938 (Box 47)
    - Montgomery, Robert H. New York Income Tax Procedure, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1921 (Box 47)
      [Inscribed by Montgomery to Wm M. Lybrand, Mar. 21, 1921]
    - Montgomery, Robert H. Fifty Years of Accountancy, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1939, 2 copies ( (Box 47)
      [One copy inscribed by Montgomery to John C. [Porter], Dec. 25, 1939]
    - Dicksee, Lawrence R.; Montgomery, Robert H. Auditing: A Practical Manual for Auditors, Authorized American Edition [Dicksee's Auditing, edited by R. Montgomery], New York, 1905 (Box 47)
    - Montgomery, Robert H.; Staub, Walter A. Auditing Principles: A Textbook, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1923 (Box 48)
    - Montgomery, Robert H.; Staub, Walter A. Auditing Principles: A Textbook. Third Printing, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1924 (Box 48)
    - Montgomery, Robert H. Prefaces to Robert H. Montgomery Federal Income Taxes: 1917 - 1950, n.p., n.d (Box 48)
  - Subseries IX.2: Books on Accounting
    - George Washington's Accounts of Expenses, Boston and New York: Houghton Mufflin Co., 1917, os) (Box 48)
    - Staub, Walter A. Auditing Developments During the Present Century, Cambridge, MA: Harvard University Press, 1942 (Box 48)
      [Inscribed by Staub to Robert H. Montgomery]
    - Staub, Walter A. Income Tax Guide: An Analysis of the Obligations Imposed on Individuals, Firms and Corporation by the Federal Income Tax Law, RBML, 1915, 2 copies ( (Box 48)
      [One copy stamped by Montgomery, signed by Walter Gee]
    - Walker, Francis A. Money In Its Relations To Trade and Industry, New York: Henry Holt and Co., 1889 (Box 48)
      [Signed by Wm. M. Lybrand, March 1892]
    - Bell, Hermon F Retail Merchandise Accounting, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1936 (Box 48)
      [ Signed by author]
    - Bell, Hermon F Retail Merchandise Accounting, Second Edition, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1956 (Box 48)
    - Bell, Hermon F Retail Merchandise Accounting, Third Edition, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1961 (Box 48)
      [Continuation of Retail Merchandize Accounting by Bell]
    - Moscarello, Louis C.; Grau, Francis C; Chapman, Roy C. Retail Accounting and Financial Control, Fourth Edition, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1976 (Box 48)
    - Bell, Hermon F Reminiscences of a Certified Public Accountant, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1959 (Box 48)
      [Inscribed by author to Audrey Rikes, Dec. 29, 1959]
    - Perry, Donald P. Public Accounting Pracice and Accounting Education, Boston: Graduate School of Business Administration, Harvard University, 1955 (Box 48)
      [Inscribed by author to Alvin R. Jennings]
    - Mahon, James J., ed. Working with the Revenue Code - 1958: Selected Comments for The Journal of Accountancy, Jul. 1954 - Jul. 1958, New York: AICPA, 1958 (Box 48)
    - Zimmerman, Robert M; Kaufman, Robert M; Finerty, Gregory S; Egan, James O. Retail Accounting and Financial Control, Fifth Edition, New York: John Wiley & Sons, Inc., The Ronald Press Publication, 1990 (Box 49)
    - Rappaport, Louis H. SEC Accounting Practice and Procedure, First Edition, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1956 (Box 49)
    - Rappaport, Louis H. SEC Accounting Practice and Procedure, First Edition, Revised Printing, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1959 (Box 49)
    - Rappaport, Louis H. SEC Accounting Practice and Procedure, Second Edition, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1963 (Box 49)
    - Rappaport, Louis H. SEC Accounting Practice and Procedure, Second Edition, Revised Printing, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1966 (Box 49)
    - Rappaport, Louis H. SEC Accounting Practice and Procedure, Third Edition, New York: John Wiley & Sons, Inc., The Ronald Press Publication, 1972 (Box 49)
    - Halper, Stanley D; Davis, Glenn C; O'Neil-Dunne, P. Jarlath; Pfau, Pamela R. Handbook of EDP Auditing, Boston - New York: Warren, Gortham & Lamont, 1985 (Box 49)
    - Murphy, Michael A.; Parker, Xenia Ley Handbook of EDP Auditing, Second Edition, Boston - New York: Warren, Gortham & Lamont, 1989, 2 copies ( (Box 49)
      [One copy signed by authors]
    - Murphy, Michael A.; Decker, Albert H.; Parker, Xenia Ley Handbook of EDP Auditing, Second Edition 1993 Cumulative Supplement, Boston - New York: Warren, Gortham & Lamont, 1992 (Box 49)
    - Pomeranz, Felix; Cancellieri, Alfred J.; Stevens, Joseph B.; Savage, James L. Auditing In The Public Sector: Efficiency, Economy and Program Results, Boston - New York: Warren, Gortham & Lamont, 1976, 2 copies ( (Box 49)
      [One copy inscribed by Pomeranz and Cancellieri to C&L, Mar. 22, 1977]
    - Bacas, Paul E.; Madden, John T.; Rosenkampff, Arthur Henry Auditing Procedure, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1937 (Box 49)
      [Inscribed by Paul Bacas to Col. Montgomery, Oct. 18, 1937]
    - Cooper, Vivian R. V. Manual of Auditing, London: Gee & Co., 1966 (Box 49)
      [Inscribed by [Henry Burson] on behalf of the many outors of this work, Jul. 1966]
    - Cooper, Vivian R. V. Manual of Auditing, 1969 (Box 49)
    - Kaufman, Felix Electronic Data Processing and Auditing, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1961, 2 copies ( (Box 49)
    - Sinclair, Prior Budgeting, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1934 (Box 49)
      [Signed by author - author's copy]
    - Heiser, Herman C. Budgeting: Principles and Practice, New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1959 (Box 49)
      [Both copies inscribed by author, May 1959. first to Norman Auerbach; second to William Lybrand]
    - Ovens, George; Beach, Donald I. Business and Securities Valuation, Toronto: Methuen Publications, 1972 (Box 49)
    - Chippindale, Warren; Defliese, Philip L. Current Value Accounting: A Practical Guide for Business, New York: AMACOM, 1977 (Box 49)
    - Lane, Jerome J; Mutzel, Kenneth J. Federal Income Taxation of Savings and Loan Associations and Thrift Insitutions, Boston: Warren, Gortham & Lamont, 1969 (Box 49)
    - Denney, Richard L; Rua, Anthony P. Federal Income Taxation of Insurance Companies, [First Edition], New York: The Ronald Press Company, 1961 (Box 50)
      [Inscibed by T. Rua to Kirk Batzer, Nov. 1961]
    - Lenrow, Gerald I.; Milo, Ralph; Rua, Anthony P. Federal Income Taxation of Insurance Companies, Third Edition, New York: John Wiley & Sons, Inc., The Ronald Press Publication, 1979 (Box 50)
    - Johnson, Kenneth P.; Jaenicke, Henry R. Evaluating Internal Control, New York: John Wiley & Sons, Inc., The Ronald Press Publication, 1980, 2 copies ( (Box 50)
      [One copy signed by Johnson]
    - Crestol, Jack; Schneider, Herman M. Tax Planning For Investors: A Guide to Securities Investment and Tax Shelters, Princeton, NJ: Dow Jones Books, 1977 (Box 50)
      [Signed by J. Crestol]
    - Crestol, Jack; Schneider, Herman M. Tax Planning For Investors: A Guide to Securities Investment and Tax Shelters, Princeton, NJ: Dow Jones Books, 1978 (Box 50)
    - Crestol, Jack; Schneider, Herman M. Tax Planning For Investors: The Eighties Guide to Securities Investment and Tax Shelters, Homewood, IL: Dow Jones-Irwin, 1983 (Box 50)
    - Crestol, Jack; Schneider, Herman M. Tax Planning For Investors: The Eighties Guide to Securities Investment and Tax Shelters, 1985 Edition, Homewood, IL: Dow Jones-Irwin, 1985 (Box 50)
    - Crestol, Jack; Schneider, Herman M. Tax Planning For Investors: The Nineties Guide to Securities Investment and Tax Shelters, Chicago, IL: Commerce Clearing House, Inc., 1991 (Box 50)
    - Halperin, Jerome Y.; Grey, Francis J.; Moser, Carl M.; Huene, Herbert A. Tax Planning For Real Estate Transactions, Prepared for Farm and Land Institute of the National Association of Realtors, 1978 (Box 50)
    - Halperin, Jerome Y.; Grey, Francis J.; Moser, Carl M.; Huene, Herbert A. Tax Planning For Real Estate Transactions. Revised Edition, including addendum on the Revenue Act of 1978, Prepared for Farm and Land Institute of the National Association of Realtors, 1978 (Box 50)
    - Millstein, David L; Ewart, James D.; Silverman, Harry L.; Grey, Francis J. Tax Planning For Real Estate Transactions, Prepared for Farm and Land Institute of the National Association of Realtors, 1988 (Box 50)
    - C&L Guide to Business Tax Strategies and Planning, New York: Simon and Schuster, 1989 (Box 50)